Now we're going to call check upkeep.
现在我们就要调用 "checkUpkeep" 了
Now here's the thing, check. upkeep is a public function.
现在是这么一回事，"checkUpkeep" 是一个 "public" 函数
So if we just run await, raffle dot check upkeep, and we pass nothing in
如果我们直接运行 `await raffle.checkUpkeep()` 并且不传入任何参数
this is going to kick off a transaction,
这就会直接开启一次交易
because hard had knows Oh, okay, it's a public function, they're clearly trying to send a transaction here.
因为 hardhat 知道，哦，这是一个 "public" 函数，显然是要发送一笔交易了
If this was a public view function, it wouldn't, it would return that view.
如果这是一个 "public view" 函数，就不会了，它会返回 "view"
But the thing is, I don't really want to send a transaction.
但问题是，我并不想真的发送交易
But I want to simulate sending this transaction and seeing what this upkeep needed would return.
我想要模拟发送交易，然后看一下 "upkeepNeeded" 会返回什么
Well, I can actually get that by using something called call static,
我可以通过 "callStatic" 来实现这一操作
I can simulate calling this transaction and seeing what it will respond.
我可以模拟调用这笔交易，然后看它会有什么回应
So instead of raffle dot, check upkeep, I can do raffle dot cost static, that check upkeep.
所以我不再使用 "raffle.checkUpkeep" 而是要用 `raffle.callStatic.checkUpkeep`
And this will give me the return of upkeep needed and the bytes perform data,
它会返回给我 "upkeepNeeded" 以及 "bytes performData"
I can extrapolate just the upkeep needed out of this return
我们可以从这个的返回中提取出 "upkeepNeeded"
or writing const upkeep needed equals this,
也就是写 `const ` 等于这个
and then I can do assert not upkeep needed,
然后再执行 `assert(!upkeepNeeded)`
because right now upkeep needed to return false.
因为现在 "upkeepNeeded" 返回的是 false
So we'll say assert, not false, which is true.
所以我们写 "assert(!false)" 也就是 true
If upkeep needed was true, then this would be false. And this would break.
如果 "upkeepNeeded" 是 true 它就会是 false，然后就会中断
So that's what we want to do.
这就是我们想要的效果
So let's go ahead, we'll run this, see if it worked.
让我们继续，运行一下，看看能否工作
Our hat test, dash dash grep.
`hh test --grep`
And we're in passing, we are in business.
我们通过了，一切正常
Awesome. So this is working perfectly.
好极了，它的运行简直完美